this is Apple number 88 and I have a
little bit of a seed that when I was in
88 I was eight and so thinking of my
eight-year-old self and my current four
and a half year old and I don't so sure
if I talked about this before it is but
having a friends out for children not
necessarily themselves their parents
should probably use it for them but
everyone regardless of their age should
have a friend at least one and so every
kid regardless of ability or
circumstance being able to go on and
find someone who appreciates them for
them who's their own age or it works
better different ages is a idea that
I've had a lot of times with my friends
with kids on the autistic spectrum or
those stories where like someone has a
birthday party and no one comes to their
birthday party and it breaks my heart I
can't I mean just that can we get
friends kids birthday parties like have
it out for that because I've been to
birthday party before where I was the
only guest it was actually fine in a
certain sense and I've been to birthday
party another time that I was the only
guest it was devastating to the child or
the parents of the child actually and so
having an app that saws problem of
everyday friendship I think is more
important but also the the special
moment friendship to especially a kid's
birthday party to have other people
there to know that there are gonna be
other people there and people that
celebrate your kid for who they are the
Sigler said yeah I know I kinda know
your to autism like that's why we're
here because what an amazing kid for
these reasons that way friendship up for
children is Apple number eight